<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://theme651-basketball-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://theme651-basketball-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://theme651-basketball-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news/tagged/hats-caps.atom"/>
  <title>Tigers - Blog</title>
  <updated>2018-09-21T05:03:09-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Tigers</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://theme651-basketball-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news/we-want-to-make-your-activities-comfortable</id>
    <published>2018-09-21T05:03:09-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-03-23T10:26:11-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://theme651-basketball-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news/we-want-to-make-your-activities-comfortable"/>
    <title>We want to make your activities comfortable</title>
    <author>
      <name>Ivan Dragon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Designers and manufacturers of world-known sporting goods are constantly working to improve the footwear and apparel for athletes, taking into the account all the details: training load, speed, sports features and a feeling of comfort. It would seem a trifle, but it helps you to distinguish branded sport products from low-grade and cheap basketball clothing and shoes.</p>
<p>We want to make your activities comfortable so we offer only quality basketball uniforms, casual clothes and shoes at affordable prices. Efforts of our team are directed at making customers’ feel trendy with the sport clothes, shoes and accessories they pick at our basketball shop. </p>
<p><iframe width="1280" height="720" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0iX7-4NW3dQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>
<p>It would seem a trifle, but it helps you to distinguish branded sport products from low-grade and cheap basketball clothing and shoes. Our online store is a perfect solution for those who love to dress stylishly, always and everywhere. </p>
<ul>
<li>Socks</li>
<li>Jerseys</li>
<li>Hats &amp; Caps</li>
<li>Essentials</li>
<li>Jordan Brand</li>
</ul>
<p>We want to make your activities comfortable so we offer only quality basketball uniforms, casual clothes and shoes at affordable prices. When you're ready to hit the court, make sure you get your kicks at our shop! It would seem a trifle, but it helps you to distinguish branded sport products from low-grade and cheap basketball clothing and shoes.</p>
<p><a href="-"> When you're ready to hit the court, make sure you get your kicks at our shop!</a></p>
]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://theme651-basketball-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news/basketball-clothing</id>
    <published>2018-09-21T05:03:09-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-03-23T10:25:52-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://theme651-basketball-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news/basketball-clothing"/>
    <title>Basketball clothing</title>
    <author>
      <name>Ivan Dragon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>We want to make your activities comfortable so we offer only quality basketball uniforms, casual clothes and shoes at affordable prices. Efforts of our team are directed at making customers’ feel trendy with the sport clothes, shoes and accessories they pick at our basketball shop. Otherwise, the heat breaks down the body that reflects not only on the sportsman performance, but also on the whole health of an athlete.</p>
<p>Our online store is a perfect solution for those who love to dress stylishly, always and everywhere. Efforts of our team are directed at making customers’ feel trendy with the sport clothes, shoes and accessories they pick at our basketball shop.</p>
<ol>
<li>T-shirts </li>
<li>Footwear </li>
<li>Balls </li>
<li>New Arrivals </li>
</ol>
<p>It’s no secret that properly chosen clothes and sport footwear are a guaranty of comfort sport activity. <strong>Are you looking for high-quality clothing for basketball? </strong></p>
<p>Designers and manufacturers of world-known sporting goods are constantly working to improve the footwear and apparel for athletes, taking into the account all the details: training load, speed, sports features and a feeling of comfort. It would seem a trifle, but it <a href="-">helps you to distinguish branded sport products </a>from low-grade and cheap basketball clothing and shoes.</p>
]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
